Adventures in Lalaloopsy Land: The Search for Pillow is a
family, animation film directed by Robert Cullen.
Peanut Big Top has a really big surprise to share with all her
Lalaloopsy friends, but Pillow Featherbed has gone missing.
So the Lalaloopsy girls set out on an adventure, along
with their pets, to find their friend.
With lots of unexpected surprises and challenges, including an impending thunderstorm, the
girls use creativity and their special talents, but nothing seems to work.
Will they be able to find Pillow in time to see Peanut's exciting surprise?
After trying almost everything, the girls realize that working
together may be the only way to find their lost friend.
This magical adventure is full of fun and friendship and it's just sew cute!
Boulder Media Limited is an Irish animation studio
founded by filmmaker Robert Cullen in 2000.
It is currently a wholly owned subsidiary of Australian media company Princess
Pictures, which purchased the company in 2022 from its previous owner, Hasbro.
The tone is lighthearted.